fapturbo.com 2018-09-01

# FapTurbo 3.0 › Privacy

Privacy Details

**Protecting Your Confidential Information**

We, at FAPTURBO, value our relationship with each of our customers, and we appreciate the trust that you have placed in us. We recognize that you have concerns about the confidential personal information we obtain about you throughout our relationship. Because protecting your confidential information is important to us, we have adopted a privacy policy which governs how the confidential information we obtain about you is used and maintained. We pledge to protect that information and ensure that it remains private. The information in this notice summarizes the categories of personal information that we collect about you, how that information is handled, and how we protect that information.

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers to anyone, except as required or permitted by law. FAPTURBO does not sell personal information obtained about you to companies that are not associated with FAPTURBO for the purpose of marketing their products or services to you.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

The privacy policy set forth in this notice applies to FAPTURBO and affiliated companies of FAPTURBO. We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources, solely for the purposes specified:

Information we receive from you on account applications or other forms, such as name, address, phone and similar information. We use this information to administer the accounts we maintain on your behalf, process transactions requested by you, respond to your inquiries, evaluate your investment needs, and identify other products and services that may interest you.

All FAPTURBO employees are instructed to use strict standards of care regarding the confidentiality of your nonpublic personal information as outlined in firm policies. Employees not adhering to our firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. We require outside companies and independent contractors to whom we provide customer information for marketing, servicing or processing to enter into a confidentiality agreement that restricts the use of the information to those purposes. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable laws to protect your nonpublic personal information.
